

HOANG TRAN NHU PHUONG

- 092 429 4185
- phuonghoang50.k43@st. ueh.edu.vn
- 180/20B Lac Long Quan, P10, District 11, TP.HCM

ABOUT ME

Applying the professional knowledge for practical work experience and adapt to the working business' environment. For long-term, I will try to bring more value to the organization, help the organization to have more opportunities to develop in the future.

SKILLS

Communication

Problem Solving

Teamwork

Adaptability

WORKING SKILLS

- · Time management
- · Goal oriented
- Future focused
- Leadership

EDUCATION

University of Economics HCMC Sep 2017 - Mar 2021 Bachelor of Business Administration | GPA: 7.5

CERTIFICATION

- Test of English for International Communication (TOEIC) Score 745
- The Internet and Computing Core Certification (IC3)

WORKING EXPERIENCE

SAPP ACADEMY

Mar 2020 - Present

CUSTOMER EXPERIENCE

- Perform the basic operations of the Reception position.
- Manage classroom progress, class attendance rate on the software like Hubspot, OMI, SAPP's Scenter.glinkproductions
- Resolve questions and problems from student.

PASAL ENGLISH CENTRE

Aug 2019 - Feb 2020

SALESWOMAN

- Find potential customers, approach them to stimulate demand.
- Telesale and consulting a course based on collected data.

ECH XANH/ ZEN BROKEN RICE RESTAURANT

Jun 2018 – Jun 2019

WAITRESS

- Perform the tasks required by manager.
- Supervise for the day's revenue and expenditure, record books and materials in stock.

EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

MEMBER OF EVENT BOARD

- Under the HR department of the Events Department, manage the work, coordinate the personnel, devise a reasonable strategy.
- Participate in interview and training programs, bonding, hold fundraising for popular volunteer programs such as Spring Volunteer, Mid-Autumn Festival, Green Summer ...

SUPPORTER

- Supporting Youth Economic, Sports Association and participating in the Women's Sports Festival.
- Join in activities of the Union Faculty such as Running for the Heart, Green Summer, Blood Donation,